SARAH JEAN S. TRAJANO

Address : #11183 Camachilli St. Nagpayong Pinagbuhatan

Pasig City

E-mail Add.: sarahjeantrajano@gmail.com

Contact No. : +69176381755



OBJECTIVES

To enhance my skills through this kind of work and apply my knowledge acquired from education and experience. I am looking forward to an opportunity where I can utilize my skills effectively to the success of the organization and further improvement of my personal skills.

EDUCATIONAL ATTAINTMENT

MASTER'S : Philippine Christian University (October 2021- August 2022)

DEGREE Masters in Information Technology

Manila

MASTER'S : Polytechnic University of the Philippines (April 2017- 2021)

DEGREE Masters in Information Technology (36 Units)

Anonas, Santa Mesa, Manila

TERTIARY : Pamantasan ng Lungsod ng Pasig

Bachelor of Science in Computer Studies Alkalde Jose St. Kapasigan, Pasig City

S.Y. 2010-2014

WORK EXPERIENCE

Office of the Presidential Adviser on the Peace Process (OPAPP)

Payapa at Masaganang PamayaNan (PAMANA) - National Program Management Office (NPMO)

Peace Program Officer II : August 2017 – Present **Administrative Officer III** : March 2017 – August 2017 Agustin 1 Building, F. Ortigas Jr. Road, Ortigas Center, Pasig City

Tasks:

- 1. Provided support coordination to the National Program Manager
- 2. Lead/Focal Person for the FY 2017 PAMANA Projects. Ensure the implementation of all projects.
- 3. Conduct assessment of all projects under FY 2017 PAMANA
- 4. Coordination with PAMANA Units and Partner Agencies regarding various PAMANA concerns (e.g. progress report submission, meetings, data validation and other clarifications)
- 5. Assisted in organizing and/or attended various meetings (e.g. Bilateral, Inter-unit, Inter-Agency)
- 6. Assisted in the consolidation and preparation of budget proposals for submission to Partner Agencies, Department of Budget and Management (DBM), House of Representatives and Senate of the Philippines.
- 7. Drafted communications, meeting highlights and regularly maintains and updates PAMANA Program files. Performed other related tasks as deemed necessary by the Assistant Secretary for Programs.

Office of the Presidential Adviser on the Peace Process (OPAPP)

Information and Communication Technology Unit

Project Developer Officer I: January 2015 – March 2017 **Admin Assistant II**: April 2014 – December 2014 Agustin 1 Building, F. Ortigas Jr. Road, Ortigas Center, Pasig City

Tasks:

- 1. Developed and enhanced Web-based System for OPAPP
 - **OPAPP Forms**
 - **SPMS**
- 2. Developed Windows-based application
 - IT Services
 - Trip Ticket System
 - Payslip Generator
- 3. Provide Technical Support and Helpdesk Support (trouble shooting)
- 4. Maintain Active Directory Server and Application Server (Microsoft Windows Server 2008)
- 5. Performs other tasks or functions that may be assigned by the Chief Admin Officer II of OPAPP Finance and Administrative Services.

Special Program for Employment of Students (SPES)

- June 2011 March 2013 Pamantasan ng Lungsod ng Pasig COOP, Pasig city Duties: Student Assistant, Encoder
- April 2011- May 2011 Rosario Health Center (SPES), Pasig city
 - Duties: Health Patrol, responsible for sorting records, encoder
- April 2012 May 2012 Post Office, Pasig City

Duties: Encoding of Records

April 2013 - May 2013 Pamantasan ng Lungsod ng Pasig Library, Pasig City Duties: Encoding of Records

TRAININGS AND SEMINARS ATTENDED

NAME OF SEMINAR : Automation Testing using Selenium and Cucumber

PLACE/DATE : MST Connects PH September 03-04, 2022

: Personal Governance Introductory Program (Webinar) NAME OF SEMINAR

: The Center for Excellence in Governance PLACE/DATE

January 26, 2022

NAME OF SEMINAR : Mastering Data with Power BI and Security (Webinar)

PLACE/DATE : Polytechnic University of the Philippines

July 2, 2020

NAME OF SEMINAR : ISO 9001:2015 Quality Management System PLACE/DATE

: Polytechnic University of the Philippines

August 2019

NAME OF SEMINAR : Data Mining and Analytics

: Polytechnic University of the Philippines PLACE/DATE

March 17, 2018

NAME OF SEMINAR : Project Development and Management Training

PLACE/DATE : University of the Philippines, Quezon City

August 2017

: Gender and Conflict Sensitivity Training NAME OF SEMINAR PLACE/DATE

: Eugenio Lopez Center, Antipolo City

December 19-20 2016

: 200-125 Cisco Certified Network Associate (CCNA) NAME OF SEMINAR

: Rivan Training System PLACE/DATE

November 20 - December 18, 2016

NAME OF SEMINAR : Sophos Technical Training

: Agustin I Building, F. Ortigas Jr. Road Pasig City PLACE/DATE

November 29,2016

NAME OF SEMINAR : Microsoft Windows Server 2008: Administering

Active Directory

PLACE/DATE : Inventive Media Unit

202 Raman Condominium 1130, Don Chino Roces Ave.,

Brgy San Atonio Makati City

July 2 – 3 2016)

NAME OF SEMINAR : Microsoft Windows Server 2008: Implementing And

Aministering Server

PLACE/DATE : Inventive Media Unit 202 Raman Condominium 1130, Don

Chino Roces Ave., Brgy San Atonio Makati City

June 11-12 2016

NAME OF SEMINAR

PLACE/DATE

: Information Systems Strategic Planning Workshop : Information and Communications Technology Office

UP Diliman

September 22-24 2015

NAME OF SEMINAR : Peace Orientation- Brown Bag Session on the OPAPP and

the

Peace Process

PLACE/DATE : AFP Commissioned Officers Club, Camp Aguinaldo, QC

August 26 2015

NAME OF SEMINAR

PLACE/DATE

: Gender and Conflict Sensitivity Training

: Balay Indang Cavite

August 21-23 2014

NAME OF SEMINAR

PLACE/DATE

: BPO Call Center Seminar

: Pamantasan Ng Lungsod Ng Pasig

September 2013

NAME OF SEMINAR

PLACE/DATE

: Career Orientaion

: Pamantasan Ng Lungsod Ng Pasig

February 12, 2013

NAME OF SEMINAR

: Ethical Hacking and Game

PLACE/DATE

: Pasig City Library February 2, 2012

CHARACTER REFERENCES

1. MARICAR MENCHIE CELESTIAL

Program Manager Office of the Presidential Adviser on the Peace Process Pasig city 09665494743

2. JAZHEEL JETT HIBIONADA

Project Development Officer IV Office of the Presidential Adviser on the peace Process, Pasig city 09175031377

3. JOHN ESTRELLADO

Peace Program Officer IV Office of the Presidential Adviser on the peace Process, Pasig city 09178233672